What's up, y'all? So as you know, I am on tour with The Unlikable Tour. Yes, I am hitting these
stages. I'm edutaining. We're laughing. We're learning. It's all the things that happen at
an Amanda Steele show. Now, y'all have told me that I should do this thing I did before again,
which is where I set up ticket donations. See, a lot of people really do want to show love,
but they're unfortunately not in the cities that I'm going to be in, or they simply just want to
give folks the opportunity to come see a show. So what you can do is you can hit the link in my
bio or in my stories. And if you want to donate a ticket or two or three or four or five,
you can hit the donate button at amandaseals.com. Folks who are interested in getting access to a
free ticket to the show in Baltimore this weekend, you just got to wait a little bit and I'll be
posting the link to the form you can fill out to hopefully get yourself a free ticket. So shout
out to everybody who has supported us in the past and shout out to everybody who's about to support
us in the present so we can all get an opportunity to listen, laugh, and learn live.
We'll see you next time.